GAYATHRI

Worked as IT Support desk Executive and completed BE(EEE). Presently working with Redington handling indigo printer's consumables.

Get in Contact: E-Mail: gayathri91eee@gmail.com Mobile: +91 9342299538

PROFILE SUMMARY

Having 8 + Years of experience in Service desk, Ticketing tool Handling, Asset management, AMC/ASC Co-ordination, and agreement Preparation, HPE- GCSN For Part Request, Care pack Registration, Handling OEM, Vendor Management & Proposal Sending. To pursue a highly rewarding career, seeking for a job where I can utilize my technical and management skills for achieving the target and developing the best performance in the organization, keep abreast with latest trends and technologies.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Support Indigo-Consumables at Genius Consultants Deputed to Redington

Aug 2023 to Present

For 6 Months Contract I joined in this organization.

- To Support and arrange consumables for HP indigo Printers for all the series.
- Need to validate and analyse the consumption/impression matching with the supplied consumables.
- Need to get an approval before processing the request.
- Once approval received as per the approval and consumption need to dispatch the consumables.
- Defectives collection/Report preparation on Monthly basis.

Last Company @ Skylark Information Technologies (IT Support Desk Executive) June 2

- June 2019 to Aug 2021
- Responds to Telephone calls and emails initiated by customers via the self-service web portal.
- Ticket raising for all the cases (E.g.: Break fix, Installation, AMC, Demo) using ticketing tool named as I-top.
- Allocation of calls to the Service Engineer and Follow up of calls till closed.
- New Installation Material delivery follow-up, Engineer assigning & Description (Installation Report) Follow up.
- HPE –GSCN Process- Part Request
- MRF (Material Requisition Form) need to raise for all the required parts using ERP Software
- 24*7 services Support for Enterprise products
- Analysis the report and provide feedback to Reporting managers.
- Customer satisfaction analysis by getting feed backs from the customer.
- Fixed support registration in HP for all sale products
- Update the License information in tool- Like VMware, Adobe, Data protector, Veeam backup, CMX backup,
 Antivirus- like Symantec, McAfee, Trend micro, ESET, Microsoft license, O365 etc
- Daily, Weekly, Monthly reports preparation
- Service diagnostic Quotation Sharing

- Spare Quotation Preparation
- Warranty updating with OEM Partners
- AMC / ASC agreement preparation and share to the customer and follow up with the customer till get the customer's approval.
- Generating Report & Droviding the feedback to the IT manager at the end of the day.

IT Helpdesk Coordinator at V Care Communications Pvt Ltd Aug 2016 to Jun 2019

- Responding to calls/Mails- Ticket Raising-Assign to Engineer & Follow Up with engineer till Calls get closed.
- Arrange spares for the pending calls.
- Assisting New joiners and Back-office Coordination.
- Quotation Preparation & Vendor
 Management
- Leading teamwork and Monitoring Team

Technical Skills

- Handling all branded computers & Laptop.
- Installation of Windows XP, Win7, Win8, Server 2003/2008, Ubuntu & Linux
- Installing and configuring local and network printers.
- Connecting the printers with the desktops & laptops
- Provide Internet, basic level network issues, backup and restore, etc.
- Provide Remote support using Team viewer.
- Configuring Microsoft Outlook.

Service Co Ordinator at Perfect Computers May 2013 to Jul 2016

- Calls attending/Allocation of calls to engineers.
- Daily call status report needs to update.
- Asset maintenance in Excel
- OS installation for all Laptops and Desktops
- Connecting the printers with the desktops & laptops
- Provide Remote support using Team viewer.

<u>Skills</u>

- MS Office
- Purchase Management
- Back Office Operations
- Customer Service & Laptop support
- IT Help Desk
- HP-GCSN
- HP Indigo Printer Consumable Analysis
- Microsoft Power Bi

ACADEMIC CREDENTIALS

Examination	Name of Institution	University/Board	Year of Passing	Aggregate
B.E (EEE)	Adhiparasakthi Engineering College, Melmaruvathur.	Anna University, Chennai	2013	86%
HSLC	Dr.K.K.Nirmala Girl's higher secondary school, Chennai.	State Board of School Examinations	2009	88.75%
SSLC	Dr.K.K.Nirmala Girl's higher secondary school, Chennai.	State Board of School Examinations	2007	83.8%

ACHIEVEMENTS

- General proficiency Award at higher secondary level.
- Won Prize in Centum Aspirants' Test.
- Bagged the Gold Medal in Anna university.
- Won Best Employee award.
- Got appreciation for good customer relation support.

Personal Details

Languages Known: Tamil and English

Hobbies: Listening to motivational Stories, Drawing, Reading Books, and Craft Work

Strength:

- Able to achieve immediate and long-term goals.
- Ability to work as individual as well as in group.
- Self-confident and self-motivation
- Willingness to learn and lead group effectively.

Marital Status: Married

Residential Address: No 35/1, Annai Sathya Nagar 3rd Street, 2nd Floor, Arumbakkam, Chennai- 600106

DECLARATION

I hereby declare that the given details are true and up to date to the best of my knowledge & belief.

Date :

Place: Chennai (GAYATHRIR)